亲爱的 伊比莎餐厅今晚只有
So, honey, Ibiza can only
六点半的时段有空位给我们
take us at 6:30 tonight.
好的 我们在伊比萨见面
Great. I will meet you at Ibiza.
正确发音是伊比"莎" 而不是伊比"萨"
It's pronounced "Ibeetha", not "Ibeeza".
多谢提醒啊 宝贝
Oh, thanks, honey.
这让我想到这周末
That reminds me - this weekend,
我想去"董"物园看小熊猫
I want to see that baby panda at the "thoo".
对对对 我是白痴
Yeah... I'm the idiot.
今年的情人节
This year for Valentine's Day,
我们要去伊比莎餐厅
we're gonna have a nice,
共进美妙又安静的晚餐
quiet dinner at Ibiza.
去年 我们...
Last year, we, um...
我们玩过火了 一点点
We overreached... a little.
我们创造了性感的第二人格
We created sexy alter egos
克莱夫和朱莉安娜
Clive and Juliana
他们是在酒店的吧台认识的
met in the hotel bar.
她在酒店大厅里
This one lost her panties
在她老爸面前失去了她的小裤裤
in the lobby in front of her dad...
-菲尔 -还挺有意...
- Phil. - Which was still
是很惨 对她来说真的很难受
it was hard. It was hard for her.
你明明知道我不喜欢你提那个字
You know I can't stand it when you use that word.
-"小裤裤"吗 -是的 就是那词
- "Panties"? - Yeah, that. Yes. That word.
对不起 她弄丢了内裤裤
Sorry. She lost her underpanties.
-怎样啊 -怎么啦
- So? - So?
如何啦 怎么样啦
Well, huh? So?
-这是干嘛 -花呀
- What's happening? - Flowers?
是有歹徒在挟持你吗
Is someone pointing a gun at you?
拜托
Oh, for goodness' sake.
你有没有收到我跟莉莉送给你的花嘛
Did you get the flowers Lily and I sent you?
真贴心 可是我真的什么也没收到
Oh, that's so sweet. No. No, I didn't get anything.
是吗 你跟你那个助理确认过了吗
Really? Did you check with that assistant of yours?
布拉德里克
Broderick!
你今天有收到花吗
Uh, did you get any flowers today?
没有 我过的是没有情人的情人节
No. Sadly, I'm without Valentine this year.
不是给你 是给米奇尔 花是给米奇尔的
No, for Mitchell! The flowers are for Mitchell!
原来如此
Oh, that's right.
抱歉
Oops.
米奇尔的助理迷他迷得无法自拔
Mitchell's assistant has a huge crush on him.
他没有
He does not.
我觉得最明智的选择
And I think the only prudent thing
就是跟他说 "你被炒了"
to do is say, "You're fired. "
别吃干醋了
Don't be jealous.
他只是比较敬重我
He just looks up to me.
米奇尔的问题就是有时候太天然呆
The thing about Mitchell is he can be naive.
他不知道自己多迷人 多招蜂引蝶
He is completely unaware of how absolutely adorable he is.
好了好了 谢谢夸奖
Oh. Okay, well, thank you.
但是要是有人迷上了我 我看得出来的
But I am aware when someone has a crush on me,
可他是真的没有迷上我
and he does not have a crush on me.
他绝对是迷上了我
Yes, he has a crash on me.
我本来还真有点担心
I was a little concerned when
他们居然只有六点半才有位置
they said they could only take us at 6:30, but...
我理解 可这里火的很啊 是吧
I know. This house is on fire, right?
你看 情人节就是应该这么过的
Now, this is how you do V-Day.
除了这里大多的人
Except most of these people
在欧战胜利纪念日[1945年]时就应该来这庆祝了
could have been here on V-E Day.
还是很有格调嘛 跟我们很搭
But it's classy, which we deserve.
是啊 绝配
Yes, we do.
去年我们是发了什么疯
What were we thinking last year,
怎么会想扮演一对年轻小情侣啊
acting like a couple of teenagers?
我知道
I know. Oh!
我们已经享受过我们的疯狂情人节了
Hey, we've had our crazy Valentine's Days.
我们玩疯到了极点
We tore it up!
可是过了之后 你不能念念不忘啊
But you got to know when to let that stuff go.
你说得对
Yeah.
现在外面的小屁孩追求的刺激
All those kids out there are
对我们而言不过是过往云烟
just looking for something that we've already got.
是的
Yeah.
-我爱你 -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you, too.
我的天呐
Oh, my gosh!
-你没事吧 -没事 我们都没事
- Are you okay? - I'm good. We're good.
您没事吧
Are you all right?
这是我第一天骑这玩意
This is my first day in one of these things.
让我来吧 我来帮你吧
Oh, hey, let me, let me help you out.
我帮你把停在那边好吗
How about I park it over there for you, okay?
谢谢你了
Oh, thank you.
这是你的停车票
Here's your valet ticket.
我开玩笑的 这是我的停车票
I'm kidding, actually. That's my valet ticket.
好了
All right.
我瞧瞧
Let's see.
左开右刹
Lefty loosey, righty tighty. Hey!
动啦
All right.
这很有趣 克莱尔 你也来玩玩
This is fun, Claire. You got to try this.
菲尔
Phil.
-他有骑这车的天赋 -谢谢
- He is the natural. - Thank you.
我知道我和菲尔会有年华老去的一天
I know Phil and I are gonna grow old together someday...
这东西需要后视镜
This thing needs mirrors.
但绝不能是情人节这天
But today is not that day.
你好
Hello?
你好 我找克莱夫
Hello, may I speak to Clive?
抱歉 你打错了 再见
I'm sorry. I think you have the wrong number. Bye-bye.
我断线了 麻烦帮我重拨一下
I got disconnected. Would you mind redialing?
你好
Hello?
你好克莱夫 我是朱莉安娜
Hello, Clive. This is Juliana.
听着女士 请别再打给我了
Look lady, please stop calling me.
-这... -别挂 菲尔菲尔菲尔 别挂
- This is... - No. Phil. Phil. Phil. Don't hang up.
-克莱尔 -不不不 不是克莱尔
- Claire? - No, no, no. Not Claire.
是朱莉安娜
Juliana.
而你是克莱夫·比克斯比 还记得吗
And you're Clive Bixby, remember?
我们去年在酒店吧台认识的
We met at the hotel bar last year.
现在找个借口 甩开你老婆
Now... make up some lie, ditch that wife of yours,
三十分钟后到那个酒店找我
and meet me at our hotel in 30 minutes.
你觉得你能搞定她吗
You think you can you manage that?
小宝贝 我都骗了她十六年了
Baby doll, I've been lying to my wife for 16 years.
很好 待会见
Okay. See ya.
要喝点香槟吗
So... Champagne?
其实 克莱尔 我有点事得去处理
Um, actually, Claire, something's come up.
所以我得先走了
So... gotta go.
不准你在情人节抛下我
You're not ditching me here on Valentine's Day.
别管那事了 坐下
Screw that. Sit.
可是... 好吧
But... o- okay.
我们 我们就待着吧
We'll - we'll stay.
-菲尔 -这也是一部分吗
- Phil. - Oh, that's part of it?
真香艳火辣
So hot!
克莱尔 我要走了 自己保重
Claire. I'm leaving. Deal with it.
现在都没人走路了吗
So, no one walks anymore!
要再等一会应该就好了
Should be just few more minutes.
我们预定是几点
When is our reservation?
情况是这样的
Here's the thing.
不 别解释 解释就是掩饰
No, not "the thing. " I hate "the thing".
我的秘书搞砸了
My secretary screwed up and
没有帮我们预订到 别担心
didn't get us one. Don't worry.
我这就过去贿赂下那家伙
I'll slip the guy a few bucks.
哪个白痴会蠢到连续两年弄砸了情人节呢
What kind of idiot messes up two Valentine's in a row?
不是我这白痴
Not this idiot.
两个月前 我预订了私人厨师
Two months ago, I booked a private chef,
还找了一乐团来演奏 叫业务乐队
musicians - the works...
为了在家里置办场浪漫的晚餐
for a romantic dinner at home.
我的任务就是把"大小姐"带出去
I just had to get the senorita out
好让他们在家里做准备
of the house while they set up.
这是五十块 千万别给我们位子
This is 50 bucks. Do not give us a table.
那你给我钱干嘛
What's the money for?
你还得婉拒我巧舌善辩的老婆的要求
You also must refuse my wife. She's very persuasive.
再等会就行了
Just a couple more minutes.
我们不会在高级餐厅弄到位子
So we don't get the table at the fancy restaurant,
歌洛莉亚就会很抓狂
which drives Gloria crazy.
"杰 你为什么不能对我浪漫一点呢"
"Jay, why you not be no more romantic to me?".
到时我们走进家门 天降惊喜
We walk in the door, and bam!
她就呆若木鸡了
She looks like a big idiot.
这不就是情人节的意义吗
And isn't that what Valentine's Day is all about?
杰 过来 我们有座了
Jay, come here. We're in.
你秘书没有忘记 看
Your secretary didn't forget. Look.
普里契特 两位
Pritchett for two.
提醒一下 我八点要看电视的
Just a reminder. I need the television at 8:00.
杰里米要和我电话约会
Jeremy and I have a phone date
要一起看《真爱至上》的
to watch "Love Actually".
这真是最逊的约会计划了 但我真妒忌
That's the lamest plan ever, and I'm jealous.
我的男友戴维
So, my boyfriend, David,
在全年最浪漫的晚上
blows me off on
竟然放我鸽子 去读书了
the most romantic night of the year - to study!
这真是最糟糕的情人节了
This is the worst Valentine's Day.
最棒的情人节啊
Best Valentine's Day ever!
戴维放了海莉的鸽子
David stands up Haley,
前男友迪兰也没戏了
and old boyfriend Dylan is out of the picture.
我不是说我想念迪兰
I'm not saying I miss Dylan,
但至少他很浪漫
but at least he was romantic.
戴维绝不会送我一瓶他流的"痴情泪"
David never sent me a jar of his own tears.
我是在放长线钓大鱼
I'm playing the long game here.
现在先喜欢我 以后再慢慢爱上我吧
Like me today, love me tomorrow.
她曾有过浪漫的男友 也有过聪明的男友
She's had the romantic. She's had the intellectual.
那一个又浪漫又聪明的
How about all of that in one fine,
棕色小男友会有多棒呢
little brown package?
-我的人生到达了新低点 -你可以跟我倾诉
- I've hit a new low. - You can talk to me.
这下我更低落了
And I'm lower.
我只是回来拿东西
Just picking up some things.
忽略我的存在吧
I am not here.
胸牌 胸牌 胸牌
Name tags, name tags, name tags.
快点 找到啦
Come on! Bingo!
我知道怎么办了
I know what to do.
迪兰又给我来短信了
Dylan's been texting me again.
我敢肯定如果戴维知道了
Bet if David knew that,
肯定会马不停蹄赶过来
he'd come running right over here.
等等 在你开始玩弄这些男人之前
Wait. Before you start playing these games,
让我问你一个简单的问题
let me ask you one simple question...
海莉·邓菲的本色为何
Who is Haley Dunphy?
-海莉 千万别这样做 -不要跟着我
- Don't do it, Haley! - Stop following me.
让我说说我的看法
Let me just say my piece.
不要
No.
听着 你可以把自己
Look, you can be the Haley
定位是戴维女朋友
who defines herself as David's girlfriend,
或是迪兰女朋友
or Dylan's girlfriend,
或者完完全全做自己
or you can be your own Haley.
虽然你还不认识本色的海莉
Maybe you haven't met her,
可我认识她
but I know her.
她是个很给力的人
She's an amazing person.
如果你准备好了 我想把你介绍给她
So when you're ready, I'd like to introduce you.
卡梅隆 有什么能为你效劳的吗
Cameron! Is there something I can do you for?
没什么 我只是来接我男人的
No. I just came by to pick up my man.
我今晚要跟他去伊比莎餐厅吃饭
I'm taking him to Ibiza tonight.
哦 听说伊比莎餐厅很不错呢
Ooh, I've heard good things about Ibiza.
但是你恐怕得和他在那里碰面了
But I'm afraid he may have to meet you there.
他现在正在开会
He's in the middle of a meeting.
在情人节晚上开会吗
On Valentine's night?
我排他行程表的时候没注意 我的错
I didn't realize when I scheduled it. It's my fault.
天啊 我太"意外"了
Gasp. I'm shocked.
等他开完会了
I could drop him off at
我可以就送他去餐厅啊
the restaurant as soon as they wrap it up.
你人"好"的像头小鹿似的
Oh, aren't you a dear?
真想就这么把你头拽下来挂墙上
I'd like to mount your head in my trophy room.
小卡
Cam!
等等
Wait.
我是不是哪方面做错 惹你生气了
Have I upset you in any way?
拜托 别装了
Oh, please. Let's not play this game.
你我早已心知肚明
We both know what's going on.
我有表现的这么明显吗
Have I been that obvious?
花都没送到
Uh, the flowers that don't get delivered,
情人节的计划也被打乱了
the Valentine's Day plans that get interrupted...
还需要说的更明白吗
Do I really need to spell it out for you?
我 米奇尔 你个小三
Me, Mitchell - wedge.
别讨厌我 我只是...
Don't hate me. It's just...
见到别人能够拥有
so hard to see someone
你想要又得不到的东西 心里堵得慌
else have something you want and can't have.
布拉德里克是否对某人有意思 没错
Does Broderick have a crush? Yes.
是不是对经常出现在办公室的某人有意思
On someone he frequently sees at the office?
没错
Yes.
那个人有红色头发和胡子吗
Does that man have red hair and a beard?
没有 但是他的男朋友有
No, but his boyfriend does.
就是我 他是对我有意思
It's me. The - the crush is on me.
你到了
This is you.
你明白我的意思吧
Oh, did I validate you?
当然
Oh, yes.
-苹果马提尼吗 -本来是的
- Appletini? - It was.
你和以前一样英气勃勃 克莱夫
You're looking handsome as ever, Clive.
你也一如往常的明媚动人 朱莉安娜
As are you, Juliana.
你性感火辣地都可以烤披萨了
You look hot enough to cook a pizza on...
乳火焚身
in.
看来你的扬声器生意赚了不少
I see the speaker business is treating you well.
我不喜欢谈钱
I don't like to talk about money...
但请完你这杯马丁尼之后
but I have exactly $10 million...
我正好还有一千万家产
minus the cost of your next drink.
两杯 只要两杯苹果马提尼
Two. Just two appletinis, please.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
这个
Yeah...
我为什么觉得你不像是真的商人
Why do I get the feeling you're not really a salesman?
挺秀外慧中的嘛
Ohh... pretty and smart.
还是该说你是 机智过人呀
or should I say "pretty smart"?
我也有在为美国政府做
I might do some high-risk work for
一些危险工作 所以经常得在国内跑来跑去
Uncle Sam that takes me clear around the country.
你意思是说你是一个
Mm, so you could say you're a...
神秘的国家干员吗
national man of mystery.
-老是没搞清你是做哪行的 -还没搞清吗
- Never did catch what you do. - Didn't you?
是还挺奇怪的 我通常
Surprising, I know. I'm usually
还挺擅长在酒吧里观察出女人的小细节的
pretty good at catching things from women in bars.
克莱夫 我只是个寂寞主妇
Well... Clive, I am just a bored housewife
暗自偷欢 仅有一小时消遣作乐
with a dark side and an hour to kill
这是我想的那个玩意吗
Is that what I think it is?
这不是张礼物卡 不过也可以是张"礼物"卡
It's not a gift card. Or maybe it is.
我去楼上等你了 克莱夫 别让我等太久
I'll be upstairs, Clive. Don't take too long.
我从不会让人等
I never do.
-杰 放松点 -抱歉 这地方太垃圾了
- Jay, relax. - I'm sorry. The place is a dump.
-这地方美极了 -菜单上没好菜
- It's beautiful. - Nothing good on the menu.
看见那个服务生的手了吗
You see the hands on our waiter?
感觉他给猪接生过一样
Looks like he's been birthing hogs.
我们赶紧打道回府吧
Let's just get out of here.
我不知道你今晚是哪根筋不对
I don't know what's wrong with you tonight,
我打扮的漂漂亮亮的 而且我饿了
but I'm hungry, I look fantastic,
所以我们留下
we're staying.
精心准备的五道菜晚餐在家里等着
Five-course dinner waiting at home,
而她却死活要在这吃垃圾
and she's strapping on the feed bag at Ibiza.
但是天堂来的天使拯救了这个夜晚
But then an angel from heaven saved the night.
你把我们预约的桌子占了
You took our reservation!
两位姓普里契特的是我们
"Pritchett for two" is us.
快点 快走 赶紧起来 快走
Come on, let's go! Move your bottom. Come on. Come on.
胖嘟嘟的同性恋天使
A big gay angel.
-喂 -喂 克莱夫
- Hello. - Hello, Clive.
你还要多久
How close are you?
我在你门口外等着呢
I am right outside your door.
-准备好了吗 -准备好了
- Are you ready? - Oh, I'm ready.
我可不这么认为 我还能听见你裤子的摩擦声呢
I don't think you are, because I can still hear your pants.
好吧 也许我应该把裤子给脱掉[闭嘴]
Well, maybe I should just shut them up.
我马上就出来
I'll be out in a minute.
我也是
So... will... I.
朱莉安娜
Juliana?
克莱夫 你在哪
Clive, where are you?
你得自己来找
You have to come find me.
哈罗
Hello?
克莱夫 我放弃 你在哪
Clive, I give up. Where are you?
我就在床上
I'm right here on the bed.
菲尔 你在几号房
Phil, what room are you in?
-菲尔是谁 -我说真的 你在几号房
- Who's this "Phil"? - Seriously, what room are you in?
-七零二号房 -我在二二六号房
- I'm in... 702. - I'm in 226.
啥
What?!
那这个是谁的房间啊
Well, w-whose room is this, then?
出了点小小的差错
There's been a tiny mistake.
还有 我想向你道歉
By the way, I need to apologize to you.
很抱歉前段时间为布拉德里克的事情闹脾气
I'm sorry I got so silly with all that Broderick stuff earlier.
没事的 这没什么大不了
Oh, please, do not worry about it.
小卡 你吃醋的样子我最喜欢了
Cam, I like it when you get a little jealous.
讨厌
Cut it out.
只要我们能达成共识
As long as we can agree
知道他对我没意思就行啦
he does not have a crush on me.
当然
Absolutely.
-那么 为了我们的爱干杯 -干杯
- So, to us. - To us.
他对你没有意思
He does not have a crush on you.
-没有 -一点都没有
- No. - Nope.
我怎么觉得你在暗示什么
Why do I feel like you're hinting at something?
米奇尔
Mitchell,
关于布拉德里克的小暗恋 我们已经谈了很多次了
we have talked long enough about Broderick's crush,
显然他根本没那个意思
which he does not have...
起码对你没意思
on you.
-天哪 你想说啥 -好吧
- Oh, my God, what? - Okay, fine.
既然你要打破砂锅问到底
Since you won't let it go...
你的助理对我有意思
your assistant is hot for me.
所以他才从中作梗
That's why he's been playing the saboteur.
你敢肯定不是因为他对我有意思吗
And you're sure it's not because he wants me?
你才说了他对你没意思
You just said he didn't.
我只是在顾及你的感受
Well, I was protecting your feelings.
他在电梯里面拥抱我了
He hugged me in the elevator.
那好 那咱家产分了
Well, pick out china
你速度搬去佛蒙特周去结婚吧
and move to Vermont.
他说看到别人拥有他所爱之人 让他生不如死
He said it kills him to see someone else have something he wants.
没错 你就是那个别人 我就是他所爱之人
Yes. Yes. You're the someone and I'm the something.
好吧 不争了
Okay. All right.
-给他打电话吧 -打电话
- Call him. - Call him?
打去问他啊
Call him.
要不要干脆直接去他家
Why don't we just go over to
咱俩各站一边
his house and stand on opposite sides of the room
看看他奔向谁的怀抱
and see which one of us he runs to?
你去结帐 我去提车
You get the check. I'll get the car.
我们才不去他家呢
We are not going over there.
也不会给他打电话
And we're not calling him.
小卡 谁在乎他迷上了谁
Cam, who cares which one of us he has a crush on?
重要的是 我迷上了你
The important thing is, I have a crush on you.
就算我的秘书也迷上了你 我不怪他
And I wouldn't blame Broderick if he did, too.
你嘴真甜
That's so sweet.
要是他迷上了你 我也不会怪他的
I- I wouldn't blame him if he had a crush on you, either.
好吧
Good.
-什么东西 "好吧" -就单纯的"好吧"
- "Good" What? - Just, good.
"好吧"意思是到此为止呢
"Good" meaning we're done with this, or
还是 "好吧"你还是觉得他迷上的是你啊
"Good" meaning you still think he has a crush on you?
得了吧 小卡
Oh, Cam!
-后者 -我这就去提车
- The second one. - I'm getting the car.
你就跟我进屋去吧
Would you please just come in the house?!
你有一整年的时间去准备 但你根本没用过心
You had a whole year to plan, but you don't make an effort.
杰 我是你的新任娇妻
I am the second wife, Jay.
为啥你对我跟对黄脸婆原配似的
Why do you treat me like I'm the first?
咱们进屋再说 你去哪
Look about it inside. Where are you going?
我要去兜兜风 我需要冷静一下
I'm gonna take a ride. I need to cool down.
你就跟我进屋吧 我保证你会感觉好一点
Just come in the house. I promise you'll feel better.
我不想进屋
I don't want to go in there.
进屋去你肯定会感觉好多的
You're gonna like it better inside.
别拦着我
Don't hold me back.
不好意思亲爱的 我得动粗了
I'm sorry about this, honey. I'm sorry.
杰 你干什么 你疯啦
Jay, what are you doing? Are you crazy?!
你在干什么啊 你疯了吗
What are you doing? Have you lost your mind?
没有 不过你马上会疯狂的
No, but you're about to.
情人节快乐
Happy Valentine's Day!
怎么了这是
What the hell?
歌洛莉亚
Gloria!
宝贝儿
Honey.
我要去兜风了
I'm going for a drive.
我本来准备了一个秘密晚餐
I had a whole private dinner planned.
结果不知道为什么变这样了
I don't know what happened.
我知道 我明白怎么回事
But I do. I know exactly what happened!
不 你不知道
No, you don't.
-什么 -我赢了
- What the hell? - I win!
我早发现你偷偷摸摸 打算耍我一下
I see you sneaking around, trying to trick me,
所以当我搞清楚之后
so when I figure it out,
就把晚餐移到这边来了 然后耍了你 我赢啦
I move the party over here, and I trick you. I win!
什么叫你赢了
What do you mean, you win?
我知道你觉得我认为你不够浪漫
I know you think I think you're not romantic,
但我觉得你认为我没你聪明
but I think you think I'm not smarter than you.
现在真相大白了
So now we know.
你够浪漫 我也比你聪明
You are romantic, and I'm smarter than you.
而且我还给你买了辆摩托
And I bought you a motorcycle.
天哪 这车真棒
Oh, my God. It's fantastic.
我又赢了
I win again!
宝贝儿 我喜欢这一切 不过情人节不是让你赢的
Honey, I love all this, but you can't win Valentine's Day.
我是说 如果你把情人节搞成一个
I mean, you defeat the whole idea
愚蠢的竞赛 那这节日的意义就没了
if you make it into some silly competition.
闭嘴吧 我赢了
Shut up. I win.
-出发吧 -我们真要去吗
- Let's go. - So we're really doing this?
-必须的 -他肯定是迷上我的
- Oh, we're doing this. - Well, it's gonna be me.
-我已经在为你等会的囧样难过了 -好吧 走
- I'm already embarrassed for you. - All right.
-等一下 -怎么了
- Oh, wait. - What?
-布拉德利克来短信了 -读出来
- Oh, it's a text from Broderick. - Read it.
"米奇尔 我相信你爱人已经告诉你
"Mitchell, by now I'm sure Cameron
在电梯里发生的一切了
has told you what happened in the elevator.
我所说的一切都是肺腑之言
While I meant every word I said,
我明白这样做十分失职
I realize how unprofessional I was.
请接受我的辞职
Please accept my resignation.
你和你爱人的感情来之不易
What you have with Cam is very special,
如果我成了第三者 我永远不会原谅自己
and I would never forgive myself if I came between you.
从心底祝福你们 珍重对方 布拉德利克"
Treasure each other. Sincerely, Broderick".
-天哪 我们在干什么呢 -我也不知道
- Oh, Cam, what are we doing here? - I don't know.
如果一个小秘书对谁着迷
Maybe if some assistant's crush
值得我们如此大动干戈的话
is so important to us,
我们真应该更加珍惜对方
it means we should appreciate each other a little bit more.
是啊 这正是个重新开始的好时机 来吧
Well, I can't think of a better time to start. Come here.
而短信最棒的地方就在于
And the great thing about that text
我们无需知道他到底迷上了谁
is we don't have to know which one of us he wanted.
我知道
I know.
你在这干什么呢
What are you doing?
情人节还没结束呢 朱莉安娜
Valentine's Day isn't over yet, Juliana.
亲爱的 别强求了
Sweetie, let's not push it.
你今晚可是差点进警局了
You almost got arrested tonight.
那今晚就这么不了了之吗
That's how it's gonna be?
-你就这么放弃我们的感情吗 -我不是放弃
- You're just giving up on us? - I am not giving up on us.
我只是放弃了克莱夫和朱莉安娜
I am giving up on Clive and Juliana.
等一下 等等 等等
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
我知道有不少男女都有本事挽回这局面
I know a couple of people who could possibly save this night.
或许你知道他俩
Maybe you've heard of them...
两个美国青年尽他们所能
"Two American kids, doing the best that they can..."
菲尔和克莱尔
Phil and Claire Dunphy.
我今晚绝对不会再回那个旅馆了
I am not going back to that hotel tonight,
而且我肯定你被禁止进入了
and I'm pretty sure you're not allowed to.
不需要 菲尔和克莱尔有间卧室
Don't need to. Phil and Claire have a bedroom,
他们随时可以把那间卧室当成旅馆
which they can turn into a hotel whenever they want.
但是孩子们
But the kids...
他们不会料到我们这么早回家
They're not expecting us home this early.
如何 你准备好去冒险了吗
So, you up for a little adventure...
克莱尔
Claire?
你觉得你能搞定吗
Do you think you can handle it...
菲尔
Phil?
"戴维 我无法成为你理想中的女孩
"I can't be the girl you want me to be, David.
我只能做我自己 再见了 海莉"
"I can only be me. Goodbye. Haley."
发送
Send it.
-我犹豫不决 -来吧 我帮你发送
- I don't know. - Here, I'll help you.
别 别 别
No, no, no, no, no!
哇
Wow.
感觉真棒
That feels really good.
因为你自由了
Because you're free.
可我很害怕 我从九岁开始就从未单身过
And really scary. I haven't been single since I was 9.
所以你应该开始慢慢来
That's why you need to take your time now...
在你做任何决定之前必须先了解自己
Really get to know yourself before you make any decisions...
大概花五六年吧
Five, six years maybe.
要数以年计吗 我得给戴维打电话
Years?! I have to call David.
打电话给一个情人节把你置之不理的人吗
The boy who tossed you aside on Valentine's Day?
不需要
No.
你配得上更好的人 海莉
You deserve better, Haley,
一个梦想家 一个诗人
a dreamer, a poet.
等着他出现吧
Wait for him.
他说不定就近在眼前
He may be closer than you think.
你听见音乐声了吗
Do you hear music?
当然 你之所以也能听见是因为
Yes, and the fact that you hear it, too...
是迪兰吗
Is that Dylan?!
天哪
Oh my God!
*想象我赤身裸体*
*Imagine me naked.*
我真是个坏到连这个都能无视的家长吗
Am I a bad enough parent to ignore that?
没错 你可坏了
You are. You're really bad.
*为你舍弃朋友也愿意*
*Without my best friend.*
你看 如果你是之前那个海莉 早就
You know, the old Haley would have...
-我爱你宝贝 -海莉
- I love you, baby! - Haley!
干杯 杰
Salud, Jay!
-我的背挂彩了 -菲尔
- There's my back. - Phil.
-不用找零了 -谢谢
- Oh, no, keep the change. - Oh, thanks.
你是不是又在里面多放了一块提拉米酥啊
Did you put an extra tiramisu in here?
-算是吧 -雷恩 老照顾我们不太好吧
- Maybe. - Ryan, again?
我只是很喜欢来你们这嘛
I just like coming here.
我跟你说 如果你是单身的话
I tell you, if you were single...
-雷恩 -雷恩
- Ryan! - Ryan!